Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
I swear to God, I didn't touch shit!
So the gate just opened up all on its own,
like magic?
It must've been some kind of malfunction.
Let me get this straight.
There was a malfunction
at the exact moment that truck showed up?
You expect me to believe that, soldier?
I swear. I don't know what happened.
What if it was a malfunction?
Only one not caused by us.
All right, lab rats, let's scurry up.
An entire dimension's about
to come crashing down on our heads.
Hey.
Is everything okay?
Listen,
I know this plan is totally mad,
and a million things have to go right,
and a million things could
and probably will go wrong.
But we can do this. I know it.
One last fight,
and this whole nightmare, it'll be over.
It'll finally be over.
Well, hello there.
MAC, this is Wolfpack. Do you copy--
- What do you think you're doing?
- Alerting the Doc.
That bitch has a God complex.
All she'll do is slow us down.
No.
We're bagging this freak ourselves.
- Do you think they're all right?
- The truck is faster than a Humvee.
Let's be conservative,
say five miles faster.
They had a six minute,
20 second head start,
giving them an additional lead
of about half a mile.
So they're fine for now,
but the real shit hasn't started yet.
Erica, language, please.
This isn't Intro to Science.
This situation demands cussing.
- So, how's it feel?
- What?
Helping to save the world and all that.
It feels pretty swell.
Pretty goddamn swell.
Go! Go! Go!
Breach! Move, move, move!
Hey, Robin, yeah.
Can you please tell me that
that was you guys
and not more of those, like, mutant Cujos?
It's us, and it's too early
to be stressed, Vic. Save it for later.
Yeah, no, copy that, yeah. No.
Bottling... Bottling emotions.
No sign of an evil moving planet.
Well, that's good.
'Cause this is gonna take some time.
All right, we should split up.
Use both ladders.
Don't rush. Pace yourselves.
There are platforms along the way,
so use them to rest.
All right.
Let's do this.
You okay?
Don't be frightened.
These are all friends.
They're just here to watch.
Don't focus on them.
Yes, Papa.
And let there be light.
All right, nice work, Bald Eagle.
Now get up to the roof.
Careful with that C-4.
I don't wanna blow the Upside Down
with us in it.
Oh, I was planning on carelessness.
But you're right, Jim.
Caution here would be wise.
All right.
Now remember,
two slow knocks means...
- The Abyss started to move.
- That's right.
And you and your sister get in position,
but you wait. You do not attack.
The second I get confirmation
that planet's close enough to the tower,
then I'm gonna give you three fast knocks.
Then we strike. We kill Henry.
And we, uh, pray to God Dustin's right,
and that planet stops moving.
What could possibly go wrong, right?
If something does go wrong,
I need you to promise me
you won't pull me out.
Not until I'm sure he's dead.
Okay, well,
then I'm gonna need a promise
from you too.
If by some miracle this plan works,
we're getting the hell out of here.
Doc Kay and her plans,
that's a problem for another day.
Deal?
Let's end this, kid.
- You want some?
- Yeah.
Hey, um...
What you said earlier at the Squawk...
I'm sorry.
I mean, not sorry about what you said.
That came out wrong.
Or not came out wrong. Jesus Christ.
It's okay.
No, it's... it's not.
I should have been there for you,
and I wasn't.
And I guess I was just so self-absorbed
that I couldn't see it.
I just... I feel like an idiot, and I...
I'm sorry.
You don't have to be sorry.
And you are not an idiot. You're not.
It's just...
I didn't even understand it myself
for the longest time.
I just... I think it needed to happen
the way it happened.
I needed to find my own way.
But what matters is
that you're still here,
and you still think we can be friends.
Friends? No, thanks.
Best friends.
All right, come on.
We've got a planet to catch.
What the hell is taking them so long?
I don't know. Maybe it has something to do
with the fact that it's a 500-foot tower.
If something's wrong, they'll contact us.
Yeah, no, yeah.
I mean, unless they're already dead.
Okay, uh, stress gives me
the munchies, so I, um...
Do you want anything?
No.
Okay.
Actually, can I get a--
Vickie?
Vickie!
Holy shit.
Mm. I swear to God,
nothing cures anxiety quite like a bowl--
Trippy, isn't it?
Hi.
Thanks, man.
Okay.
It's pretty damn spectacular.
It's almost too bad
we have to blow it all up.
Mother of God.
Jim, do you, uh, copy?
Yeah, yeah, copy.
Well, I got some good news, bad news.
Uh, good news is our theory was correct.
A giant planet is descending
upon our heads.
The bad news is our theory was correct.
A giant planet is descending
upon our heads.
- How long do we have?
- Not long.
Supergirl better be close in there.
Come on, El.
So this is Vecna, right now in the Abyss?
You don't have to whisper, but yes.
Okay, so why don't we just kill him
right here?
I mean, he seems pretty damn vulnerable.
We can't hurt him here.
We have to enter his mind.
- Isn't this his mind?
- No.
- It's my mind.
- What?
Hold on.
Are you okay?
Oh, great.
I've really missed this.
Hop.
The Abyss is moving.
- How close are we to Henry's house?
- Not close.
- How not close?
- I'm not sure.
You said you know his mind
backwards and forwards.
Yeah, I do, but there are a shit ton
of memories in here.
We're like Dorothy in Oz,
except there's no Yellow Brick Road.
Everything connects,
but there are long ways and short ways.
- Well, we need a short way.
- Yeah, no shit.
Now can you just stop talking
while I try and think?
- Joyce, this that stupid play of yours?
- Better see you there, Harrington.
Yeah, on a Friday night? You wish.
Come on, I have an idea.
- Is that Joyce?
- Yep.
And through that door,
Hop's sneaking a joint.
And that way, Mr. Wheeler
is feeling up Mrs. Wheeler.
I wish we had time to sightsee,
but we've got a play to catch.
Three, two, one, go!
Yeah, we're gonna sweep around the back.
West room's clear.
South side!
We are at location. Negative on...
No, no, no, guys. It's not lining up.
What do you mean?
Look. The tower needle,
it's not lining up with the rift.
Shit.
- If the Abyss hits the needle...
- This tower's going down.
That's great. That's just great.
Hey, Chief,
we're gonna need El to stop this planet.
- On the sooner side, please.
- How soon?
Thirty seconds?
What are we doing?
- Waiting.
- For what?
Three. We need to strike.
Chief, talk to me.
What's going on in there?
I don't know. I can't talk to her.
I gave her the signal.
Well, nothing's happening over here,
and we're about to be squashed
by a moving planet. So give it again!
- We have to go.
- This is the only way. Just trust me.
Shit!
Look out! Look out! Look out!
Now!
Steve!
Just hold on! I got you. Just hold on!
We're alive! We're alive!
Shit, I thought you were toast.
The Abyss stopped! El got him!
I repeat, El got the bastard!
Yes! Wow! Come on!
You came back. You came back for me.
And I'm not leaving your side, ever again.
Not until we're out of here. All of us.
It's her! It's the monster!
- Get up!
- No, I'm not the monster.
And I can prove it.
All clear!
Hold this.
- Hey!
- Easy!
- You ready?
- Ready?
Yeah.
Okay, easy. Easy. I got you, man.
All right, here goes nothing.
Holy shit.
Does this officially make us
space travelers?
Interdimensional space travelers.
Suck it, Armstrong.
It's over.
Where are they?
With Max.
Safe.
Where are they?
I told you.
With Max.
Far away from here.
You can't believe it, can you?
That they would ever
see through your lies.
Why can't he see us?
Because Mr. Whatsit isn't the only one
with magic powers.
That's why you take children.
Because you think they have weak minds.
But they're smarter than you think.
And you?
Are you smart?
You let yourself get caught.
And in here...
I will find all the answers I need.
Holy shit.
It's him. He's the Black Thing.
Everything Holly told you is true.
He is trying to destroy our world.
But he can't do it, not without you.
We have to escape. Right now.
Stronger, aren't we?
So am I.
Holly!
I can follow her into his mind.
We can end our brother, together.
Come on!
Now!
Hello, brother.
Don't know about you guys,
but I was expecting more like...
- Deadly vines?
- Or monsters?
I assume the hive mind works here too.
So if Henry died,
- so did all his nasty, little minions.
- "If"?
We don't know what's going on in the mind.
I know El broke the spell
and stopped the Abyss,
but she could still be fighting him.
Hey. She's been training for this.
And she's not alone.
She's got Kali and Max.
And I'm sure Henry's dead.
And if he's not, he will be.
Yeah.
Great job keeping the morale up.
Hey, man.
Hey.
Thought I was a goner back there.
Owe you one.
Yeah.
Look, just because I don't like you,
doesn't mean I want you dead.
And I've got a feeling
we're gonna need you up here.
I don't blame you, by the way.
For not liking me.
You know, I can be a real prick sometimes.
Yeah.
I mean, same.
Look, Steve,
when I was away in California,
you were there for Nancy
when I couldn't be.
And I thought that, you know,
that was why things were off with us.
But the truth is
our problems had nothing to do with you.
It just took me a long time
to figure that out.
And...
to let her go.
If we hadn't been so busy fighting,
I probably could've saved you
a little bit of time, because...
I've known for a while now me and Nance
were never really in the cards.
You know, she's independent.
She's gotta get out there, and...
- I don't know. I want...
- Six little nuggets?
She told you that?
You think it would've been better
if I'd said four?
Maybe just not calling them nuggets.
Right.
Listen, bottom line, end of the day, I...
I'd rather have her as a friend
than nothing at all.
You know, she's... she's just really...
- Special.
- Yeah.
I guess we can agree on one thing.
Yeah, I guess so.
- I still don't like you, though.
- I wouldn't want it any other way.
Hey, lovebirds!
You're gonna wanna check this out.
Jesus Christ.
That's it.
That's what I saw in my vision.
The kids are in there.
Then what are we waiting for?
Derek? No! Derek, you have to keep going.
- I can't.
- Derek, what are you doing? Come on!
Just leave me!
Save yourselves, you dumbasses!
No, don't be an idiot!
- I'm not being an idiot!
- Yes, you are! No, you can't--
- Is everyone okay?
- Yeah, we're okay.
- Did you find him? Tell me you found him.
- He just vanished.
He went back to the real world.
He can come back. Will come back.
How far to the cave?
It's not far. Come on.
Derek, we gotta go. Right now.
Go! Run!
Dustin! Lucas!
What's going on? Come on, talk to me!
You knew this would happen.
Just like you know
what will happen to her.
Don't you see, Jane?
It's a cycle.
It's a terrible, vicious cycle.
But we can stop it. Tonight.
How?
After we kill our brother,
after the children are rescued,
we don't leave with the others.
We stay on the bridge.
When the Upside Down vanishes...
so will we.
It is the only way, Jane.
The only way.
She's going to do it, Jim.
She's going to end her life.
Show yourself!
Show yourself, you lying bastard!
I am many things, but I am not a liar.
I have seen into her mind,
and now I have seen into yours.
What rage it holds!
One daughter dead because of you,
and soon another.
Show yourself!
You are as you fear.
You are the curse.
No!
Why's he signaling?
- That's not a signal.
- Then what is it?
Oh, God.
Holly!
Get to the cave!
I got you. Hang on.
Hang on!
Hold on. Hold on.
What did you do?
Hi there.
Hey, Doc.
Kids left out their homework.
- Max!
- What happened?
She just poofed away like a goddamn ghost!
Was it the Black Thing?
Did the Black Thing take them?
Listen up!
We keep to the plan. Get to the cave.
The Black Thing can't hurt us there.
So follow me, keep quiet, and stay close.
- Let's go! Come on.
- Come on, guys.
Let's go! Hurry!
The kids are all alone in there.
You have to get us back to them.
I can't, not without the bath.
He locked us out.
We have to get to the Abyss,
join the others. We can kill him there.
There is no time. The worlds will collide
long before we reach him.
Not if Holly and the kids make it
to the cave.
If Dustin is right,
without the kids, Henry can't do anything.
That's a lot of ifs.
What do you wanna do?
We can't give up, not now.
Isn't that exactly what you're doing?
Giving up.
I know the truth.
Henry showed me your plan.
Henry lied to you.
He tricked you.
He used you, and you fell for it.
Then look me in the eye and tell me.
Tell me.
Tell me you don't plan
on killing yourself tonight.
We don't have time for this.
We have to go.
I won't detonate it.
- I won't.
- What?
I will not detonate the C-4,
not until I know that you are safe
with the others back in Hawkins.
If we kill Henry and don't destroy
the Upside Down, nothing matters.
Which is why I will destroy it
once I know that you're safe.
Why are you doing this?
Because Henry's gotten to him,
and he's lost his mind.
- Kali, wait.
- No. This is bigger than him, Jane.
- Bigger than any of us.
- Yeah, go ahead. Go ahead. Shoot me.
If I'm alive, then so is Henry.
I have to end the cycle.
You will. You will. But not like this.
Not with more violence.
Not with more pain.
There's already been so much pain.
From the moment you were born.
Your mother was taken from you.
Your childhood was taken from you.
You've been attacked, manipulated, abused
by terrible people.
Life has been so unfair to you,
so cruel.
But you never let it break you.
And I need you to fight, kid.
I just need you to fight one last time.
Fight for the happy days
on the other side of this.
Fight for...
for a world beyond Hawkins.
Fight for that day
that you have a kid of your own,
and you give her the life
that you never had.
For the day you get so angry
because she invites some boy over,
and she won't keep the door open
three inches.
I know.
I know you don't believe
you can have any of this.
But I promise you
we will find a way to make it real.
You will find a way to make it real.
Because you have to.
Because you deserve it.
Jim!
Jim! Are you there, Jim?
I don't want to add to the stress,
but we've got company.
Come on! Come on!
We're almost there! Keep going!
Through this gap right here! Right here!
Come on! One by one!
Go! Go! Go!
Debbie, wait!
Have you seen Derek?
- Derek!
- Wait! Holly!
- Holly!
Come on! Come on! We got this!
We gotta go! Come on! Hurry up!
Keep running! Come on, Derek! Come on!
Get inside. He's coming! Go!
Come on!
Holly!
Go!
- Suck my fat one!
- Come on!
Holly!
- Are you okay?
- We're okay. We're okay.
Was it him? Was it Henry?
Yes, but he can't get us. Okay?
Not in here. We're safe now.
- Okay.
- We're safe.
- Why are you staring at me?
- I'm not!
We're just getting really close, okay?
And we don't know what's in there,
so I think you should be sharing
some of that firepower.
You have firepower.
Three Molotovs? Come on!
Unless you're okay living
with the guilt of my death,
I'm gonna need one of those goddamn guns!
Holy shit!
Thanks!
Those are flares.
What?
Flares. She gave you a flare gun, dude.
Flare gun?
Nancy! Nancy, what the hell is this?
Are you serious?
You think this is a joke?
What the hell am I gonna do
with a flare gun?
Hey! Will!
- Will!
Hey! What is it? What's wrong?
It's Henry.
He's alive.
Resist it.
How did you find me?
They sent you.
Resist it.
Will!
What was that?
Holly?
Stay here.
What's going on? What do you see?
It's Henry. He's made it into the cave.
He's coming! Go! Go! Up here! Everyone!
Come on! Go, go, go, go, go!
Hurry! Come on, quickly! Go! Go!
He's found them.
He's found Holly and the kids.
Okay, what about El?
Do you see El? Or Kali? Or Max?
They're alone. They're all alone.
- Go! Go! Hurry!
- Come on, guys!
Could you stop him? With your powers?
I can try. Just keep going.
Go! Go!
Move! Move! Move!
Come on! Come on!
Oh, God.
Hurry! Let's go!
Quickly! Come on!
It's right up here, this hole!
Joshua, down there! Be careful, okay?
Keep moving! Thomas, you next!
Jim, do you copy?
Goddammit!
Kali.
Well, well. Look what we got here.
Your friends just left you here, huh?
Well, that's not very nice, now is it?
Hmm.
Get her out of here.
Hey. Hey.
I got you. I got you.
And I got you.
All right, listen.
Anything you see in here is not real.
It can't hurt you.
Just keep your eyes on me, okay?
- Okay.
Come on, let's go.
Keep going. Stay close.
Eyes on me, okay? Eyes on me.
Just keep moving.
Holy shitballs!
Eyes on me, Derek!
Through here. You get to the other side,
and you wait for me.
Debbie, you first.
Thomas, your turn.
- Come on, guys. Let's hurry up!
- Let's go!
- Come on! Come on! We got this.
- Hurry up, Glenn.
Go!
Tell me where the other freak is,
or this one dies right here, right now.
I don't know what you're talking about.
It's just us.
You think I'm playing a game here?
Where is she?
Okay. Oh, what are you doing, Murray?
This is not a good plan.
This is crazy.
Okay. Here goes absolutely nothing.
One last chance.
Where is she?
Go to hell.
Okay, then.
Kali.
No, no, no!
Kali. Kali.
- Get bandages please.
- Keep pressure on the wound.
Kali, look at me. Look at me.
Hang in there, okay?
I'm here. It's gonna be okay.
I'm not going to make it.
No, don't say that. You will. You will.
You will make it, okay?
Don't cry, Jane.
My story...
was always going to end here.
No.
No, no.
Holly.
Holly?
How did you find me?
Please.
Please, mister. Don't shoot.
Who are you?
Henry. Henry Creel. I live near here.
Who sent you?
Nobody sent me.
I was in the caves. I heard a scream.
They sent you. They sent you!
You're just confused. You need a doctor.
What's happening?
He's in a memory now.
And he's scared.
He's so scared.
Oh my God. Thank God. Thank God.
Thank God. Thank God.
I thought you two were goners
for a minute there.
Oh, what?
No hug from the big man, huh?
How about a "thank you
for destroying the Huey, Murray."
"That was very brave and... and..."
What's wrong?
Wait.
Kali. Where's... Where's Kali?
Oh God.
El, I'm...
I'm so sorry.
I can jump.
I can jump those boulders to the Abyss.
I'll be right there,
right at the tree. Shortcut.
Henry's still up there.
- If you fall...
- I won't.
If you make it...
I kill him.
Oh, yeah?
And then what?
When I was a kid,
and you found me in the woods...
I was scared.
Really scared.
I didn't understand the world.
I didn't understand... people.
You took me in.
Raised me.
Protected me.
Mm.
You became my dad.
But I'm not... a kid anymore.
And I'm not Sara.
She didn't have a choice to make.
But I do.
And I need you
to trust me to make the right choice.
I need you to believe in me.
Find me.
Ah!
You must resist it.
It will consume you.
It will consume all.
It wasn't you.
It was never you.
Leave me alone.
That's why the Mind Flayer didn't want you
in the cave.
It didn't want you to remember.
I said leave me alone.
You were just a kid, a kid like me.
And it used you.
It used you to bring it here.
You're just like me, Henry.
A vessel.
But you can resist it. Help us fight it.
Don't let it win, Henry, please.
Don't let it win.
No.
It showed me the truth.
It showed me that this world is broken.
That man is broken.
Don't listen to it, Henry.
It is controlling you right now.
It has never controlled me.
And I never controlled it.
Don't you see, William?
I could have resisted it.
But I chose
to join it.
Oh my God.
It needs... me.
And I need it.
We...
...are...
one.
Run!
Run! Run! Run!
Dustin!
- Come on! Come on!
- Let's go!
Come on!
Shit!
Come on, go! Go, go, go!
Run! Run! Run!
- She's hurting it.
- How?
She's fighting Vecna.
Hive mind.
So...
you truly do want to die.
- We have to help her.
- How?
The hive mind works in both ways.
If we hurt the Mind Flayer, we hurt Vecna.
What, hurt Godzilla over there?
The only way to damage anything
of that scale, we spread out.
Flank it on all sides.
Just chip away at its hit points.
"Hit points"? What are you talking about?
There.
One of us draws it to that canyon.
The rest take positions on those cliffs.
Ambush it from above.
There's just one question.
Which one of us is bait?
I am.
Go!
Come on.
No!
No, no!
There's nothing we can do!
Come on, please!
Boom!
Look out! Look out!
- This is for Eddie, you son of a bitch!
- For Eddie!
I'm not afraid anymore.
We're not...
afraid...
of you.
Yeah!
We gotta go!
Run! Shit, shit, shit!
El!
Is everyone okay?
Holly.
Holly? Can you hear me?
Holly? Holly, come on. Come on.
Nancy?
Yeah. Yeah, it's me. I'm here.
Yeah, it's me. I'm here. I'm here.
Holly?
Hey!
Hey.
Okay, get it all out.
You got this. You're gonna be okay.
Where... Where am I?
You're safe. You're safe, bud, okay?
We're here to get you home.
Yeah. Whoa!
I got you, bud. I got you.
I got you, bud. It's okay.
Please, please. Come back to me!
No!
You fucked with the wrong family.
Mom, you're killing him!
Help!
Why don't you go ahead and go home?
I didn't run away this time.
Eddie!
I love you, man.
Goodbye, Mike.
El! El, where are you?
He did not make me into this.
You did.
Will, wake up!
Go away!
I just want this to be over.
- Chief, you copy? Chief?
- Yeah, yeah, I copy. What's going on?
Well, the noseless bastard's toast.
We're back in the Upside Down,
and we have the kids.
How is everybody? Is everybody okay?
Yeah, the party took a hell of a beating,
but we're okay.
What about El?
The whole party.
So what do we say
you hit the music, old man?
Destroy the Upside Down once and for all.
Let's ditch this hellscape.
Yeah, copy that.
All right. The countdown begins.
Hey, stop!
You're gonna get it all over me!
Hey, hey, I'm nasty too.
It does stink.
How can you just leave me standing
Alone in a world that's so cold?
The world is so cold
Maybe I'm just too demanding
Maybe I'm just like my father
Too bold
Maybe you're just like my mother
She's never satisfied
Why do we scream at each other?
What are you doing? You're gonna let
more of that crap in here.
It's either that or pass out.
Because you smell like...
I actually don't know what you smell like,
but it's bad.
Assholes.
Eh?
That's good.
There she is, home sweet home.
So, Jimbo, I just gotta ask.
How does it feel?
Feels like I need a nap and a smoke.
- I thought you quit.
- Yeah.
That's why it's gonna taste so good.
Watch out!
Everyone okay?
Everyone put your hands up!
I said, hands up!
- Move!
- Hey! Get off me!
Get down! Get down! Get your hands up!
- I said hands up!
- Oh, wow!
Okay, okay.
No! No! That's my sister! Let go of me!
- Yeah, yeah!
- Okay, okay!
Let's go! Move!
- Dustin!
- Holly, what's happening?
Everybody up! Everybody up!
El? Do you see El?
Sergeant! Where's the girl?
She was right here one second ago.
She must have escaped.
Oh God.
- Mike...
- Get off me! Get off me!
You...
You have to get out of there!
You have to get out!
None of this will ever end,
not if I'm still here.
No, no. We'll figure something out.
We'll fight back. We always do.
I need you to talk to the others.
- No. No.
- I need you to thank them for me.
For being so kind to me.
And teaching me what it means
to be a friend.
No! Please don't do this.
Mike, I need you
to help them understand my choice.
But I don't. I don't understand.
I know.
But you will.
One day, you will.
You understand me.
Better than anyone.
You always have.
From the day we met...
...you've seen me.
Well, my name's Mike. Short for Michael.
Maybe we can call you El.
Short for Eleven.
The real me.
I never meant to cause you any sorrow
I never meant to cause you any pain
I only wanted one time
To see you laughing
I love you.
I love you for exactly who you are.
I only wanted to see you laughing
In the purple rain
Please don't leave me, El.
Please don't do this.
I will always be with you.
I love you.
Purple rain, purple rain
Goodbye, Mike.
Purple rain
El! El! El! El! El!
- El!
- Mike!
- Hey, don't touch her!
Get off me! Get off me!
El! El! El!
El!
El, no!
Eleven!
El!
El! El!
No!
El!
El! El!
- Check it out?
- Yeah.
Hi there, strangers. It's been a while.
I wonder... I mean...
Do you guys... even remember me?
Okay, maybe I'm being too modest.
I mean, let's be honest,
who could forget this soothing voice
with a trace of a Debra Winger rasp?
That's right. It's me,
Robin Buckley, aka Rockin' Robin.
Jimmy "Fast Hands" was kind enough
to let me back into the booth
for a guest stint,
but you're gonna have to cut me some slack
because I am feeling rusty.
I mean, what do I even talk about?
You know?
My go-to subjects are as out of date
as, well, as my friend's bowl cut.
I mean, there's no soldiers,
no fences,
no Big Brother cameras,
and the only Big Mac I can find
is a Smush Double Patty at Mickey D's.
People are happy and smiling
and going to the movies.
But hey, who doesn't wanna see
Indy's new adventure?
Shit. Uh...
There we go.
Sorry about that.
My partner in crime ditched me.
But, well, as far as excuses go,
he had a pretty good one.
Let's go, boys!
Baseball ready! Baseball ready!
- Now...
- No mental mistakes!
...I am almost
too superstitious to say this,
and I'm knocking on some wood here,
but I think the Hawkins curse
has finally lifted.
All right, Thomas.
Let's go. Here we go, man!
- But at the same time...
- Let's go.
...this isn't even the Hawkins
that I remember.
It feels so different.
But maybe it's not the town.
Maybe it's me that's changed.
We probably all have.
At least, that's certainly true
of my friends.
Who, by the way, are graduating today.
That's right, Hawkins High class of '89
is walking the podium today.
I hope you all come out and support them.
I know I will.
Because if anyone deserves a standing O,
they do.
So to get their party started,
a new favorite.
You break any more bones,
you're on your own.
Because I am done with hospitals.
Maybe I should be on my own.
I mean...
what is going on here?
What? We're graduating today.
In two hours.
I think you're getting ahead of yourself.
Hmm.
Okay, now you're definitely
getting ahead of yourself.
I'm sorry. You're just looking,
uh, super sexy right now.
And you're looking super dorky.
Here comes your man
Ugh, gag me with a spoon.
You gonna take the picture?
Already? Please?
Ma, it's okay.
- I'm only a day's drive away.
- I know.
I'm gonna come home
every chance that I get.
Okay.
I'm gonna call you so much
that you're gonna wanna change numbers.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Okay.
- I love you.
Do you wanna take more pictures?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Ooh, so handsome. My valedictorian.
Superman!
- All right, rolling.
- Happy graduation.
Happy graduation.
- That's nice.
- Class of '89.
Yeah.
Shit. Hold on. No, no.
- Oh God. No.
- Let him hang it back up.
- Leave the bedsheet.
- No, no, no.
There's too much light.
It needs diffusion.
- It's not The Godfather.
- I know it's not.
- Let him hang it up.
- You get one more take.
It's been all day 'cause of the artist...
- Hello?
- Joyce. This is Karen. Have you seen Mike?
No, I haven't seen him.
We haven't seen him since last night.
It's Karen. She can't find Mike.
Here comes your man
El! El!
El!
Hey, kid.
Thought I might find you here.
Your mom's freaking out.
Can't say I blame her. I mean...
I don't know if you remember,
but we do have a history
of kids going missing in this town.
She won't understand.
She'll never understand why I can't do it,
why I can't walk the stage.
It'd be like a lie.
Like I'm okay with moving on.
And I'm not.
I'm not okay with it.
I had this plan.
That me and El, we were gonna go
someplace far away,
and... and no one would find us.
And I said this thing about going
somewhere with three waterfalls.
I mean, I... I don't even know
if she believed me.
Who would? Three waterfalls?
I mean, that's so stupid, childish.
It was a fantasy plan.
I should've had a real one.
I just didn't...
I didn't think that she would just...
Hey, hey. This...
It's not your... It's not your fault.
What happened is not your fault.
El made her choice.
Now it's time for you to make yours.
And the way I see it,
you got two roads ahead of you.
You got one road
where you keep blaming yourself
for what happened.
You keep going over it in your head,
what you could've done differently.
You push people away, and you suffer,
because that's what you think you deserve.
And then there's another road...
where you find a way
to accept what happened.
Find a way to accept her choice.
Doesn't mean you gotta like it.
Doesn't mean you gotta understand it.
And never think about it.
You just accept it.
And you live the best goddamn life
you can.
I've been down that first road before.
And I don't recommend it.
And as for El...
I think you know
what she would have wanted for you.
- I don't know. Me?
- Yeah.
- Never been.
- Me neither. But I think she'd like it.
Good afternoon, everyone,
and welcome to the graduation ceremony
for the class of '89.
Mom! Mom!
Mike.
I'm sorry, Mom. I panicked.
You don't have to explain.
God, look at you.
You're all grown up.
I'm so proud of you.
I'm so, so proud.
I love you, Mom.
I love you, baby.
And now it's my great pleasure
to introduce someone
who has truly excelled
during their time here.
Ladies and gentlemen, give a warm welcome
for your valedictorian, Dustin Henderson.
Yeah, buddy!
Dustin!
That's my friend!
Whoo!
I just wanted a normal childhood.
But that childhood was stolen from me.
It was stolen from us.
And this past year,
if you wanna know the truth,
I've been pretty pissed off about it.
Language.
But then I thought back
to the past six years,
and I realized that,
even though there was a lot of bad,
there was so much good too.
There's this game I like to play.
It's called Dungeons & Dragons.
- Yup!
- Jesus Christ.
And in this game,
there are two types of chaos classes,
chaotic good and chaotic bad.
Now, bad chaos brings
anarchy, destruction, war.
But good chaos can bring innovation,
change.
And this school,
frankly, it needed to change.
Because we were so divided
into the jocks, the nerds, freaks.
And in the chaos,
all those walls broke down,
and I made new friends.
I made friends who were never even
supposed to be my friends.
This wasn't just me.
I saw this happen with so many others.
When you get to know people
who are different from you,
you begin to learn more about yourself.
You change.
You grow.
I'm a better person now.
I'm a better person because of them,
because of my friends.
So, I'm not pissed off anymore.
But I am worried.
Worried,
because now that the chaos is over,
Principal Higgins
and every square like him
is gonna do their damnedest
to put everything back in order.
And I don't want order,
which is why it's hypocritical
that I'm wearing this thing.
I mean, we look ridiculous.
What is this? We look like Roman senators.
I mean, it's not who I am.
I don't think it's who any of us are.
So, honestly, just screw it.
- Henderson.
- Yes!
- Screw the school.
- Henderson! Henderson!
- Screw the system.
- That's enough!
Screw conformity.
- Screw everyone and everything...
- Yes!
...trying to hold you back
and tear us apart,
because this, this is our year!
- Yeah!
Yeah!
Whoo!
Whoo-hoo!
The bugle sounds, the charge begins
But on this battlefield, no one wins
The smell of acrid smoke
And horses' breath
As I plunge on into certain death
Whoo-hoo!
Settle down!
Back in your seats now!
Summer school for all of you!
And detention!
- Dustin!
Dustin!
You're a madman.
You're an absolute madman.
- Higgins totally shit his pants.
- What's he gonna do, expel me?
- You're crazy.
- Hey.
Hey, Stacey.
I just wanted to say what you did up there
was pretty badass.
Oh. Thanks. I was kind of just going
for a bit of a Belushi thing.
But if he was in like a Hughes film.
But I don't know. Does that make sense?
Yeah.
- That's okay if you...
- No, totally.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay. Cool.
- Why'd I say that?
- Dude...
Hey, so I'm having a party later tonight.
You guys should come.
- Wait.
- Did that just happen?
Should we go?
Is that rhetorical?
No. Screw that.
I got a better idea.
Way better.
I'm just saying, I think
you guys would really dig New York.
- Yeah.
- How much is rent?
- Thinking about moving?
- You wanna come live with me?
You're serious? Come on.
I mean, look at this place.
The sunset, the view.
Whoo!
You guys are seriously telling me
you don't miss any of this?
Mm.
No.
The forest, the quarry,
Family Video, the Hawk?
No.
No, I couldn't come back here
if you paid me a million bucks.
Mm. You'd need a lot less than a million,
I'll tell you that.
Prices are still way down.
There's actually this rad place
over in Forest Hills.
I can't quite afford it yet,
but I'm close.
And that is on a coach's salary.
- Don't forget sex ed teacher.
- That's true.
They have you teaching sex ed?
It's part of the gig.
If I had a question about an STD,
you'd be the first person I'd come to.
Thank you?
No, I love it.
I love teaching these kids, you know?
I get to teach them
about the miracle of life,
and how to not start it accidentally.
And this time,
I'm in control of the grades.
And why do I feel
like you go pretty easy there?
I have a strict A policy.
- Uh-huh.
- B, if you're a real knucklehead.
That's about as low as I go.
Hell, can you come and teach at NYU?
I mean, what, I'm gonna grade your movie
about capitalism,
cannibalism, or whatever?
No, it's anti-capitalist. The Consumer.
It's a metaphor. The more she eats,
the hungrier she gets.
- Right.
- Okay.
- Well, I mean, it's a working...
- Obviously.
- That's the working title.
- It's good.
Mm-hmm.
Now, Smith. Smith, I... I would consider.
Oh, really?
Is it the lectures on Steinem
that draw you
or the high concentration of women?
Can't it be both?
What about you, Nance?
How are the babes at Emerson?
Oh, um...
I wouldn't know.
I dropped out.
No way. What?
Ho, ho, ho! I knew it.
You became a Navy SEAL.
Oh no, not quite. I...
I took a job at the Herald.
Which... It sounds fancier like that.
It's a trainee position.
But I don't know.
I was just sick of school
and thought I'd maybe get out there
and... try the real world.
Nancy Wheeler.
Still full of surprises.
You know,
there actually is something
that I miss about this place.
I miss this.
Just...
us.
Hanging out.
I miss you guys.
I really like my new friends.
But it's...
It's not the same.
I don't think it ever will be.
Okay, Jesus.
You're killing me, man.
Let's do something about it.
I don't know. We could...
meet up.
Once a month, here.
Yeah, or... or maybe somewhere
just more neutral.
- Like...
- Okay.
What's a city between Hawkins,
and Massachusetts, New York?
Louisville.
- Uh, Philly.
- Philly.
I have an uncle who lives in Philly.
He's weird, but he's got a big house.
- Does it have a basement?
- Yeah.
- And a boiler room?
- A boiler room?
Yeah.
Oh my God, it's perfect.
You know, for the hideout.
You know, where she traps all the men
and then burns their bodies.
- The Consumer.
- What do you think I'm talking about?
- I thought you were trying to kill us.
Oh no.
Okay, okay. Yeah, so we'll meet
at Robin's weird uncle's house,
and we'll drink and reminisce
and make Jonathan's
anti-capitalist cannibal movie.
Starting next month.
Yeah, I'm in.
I'm in.
To nothing ever keeping us apart.
Including overbearing significant others.
School.
Mortgages.
And kids.
- Cheers.
Yeah, Steve. Kids?
I don't know, guys.
I think Kristen might be the one.
So, didn't you say the same thing
about Dawn?
- No.
- And Margaret.
And Julie.
I did not say that about Julie.
She was drama from the start.
Drama?
Like, is she a good actor?
Yeah, you do not wanna...
I mean, I'm looking.
- No, no, no. Not there.
- Yeah, have her come along.
Chief. Mrs. Byers. Always a pleasure.
Are we ready to order?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah. We're gonna have a bottle
of the Cabernet Sauv...
- Sauvignon.
- Yeah. Cabernet Sauvignon.
And we'll have some caviar to start.
And we will have
two of the filet specials,
however the chef would like
to prepare them.
- Very good, sir.
- Okay.
- Hop!
- What?
It's a big day.
It's a once-in-a-lifetime day.
You raised two beautiful boys
into incredible men.
They had a lot more to overcome
than just puberty.
You should be happy.
You should be proud.
I am, but...
It's just...
It's gonna be quiet in that cabin.
It's just us and the crickets.
Ugh, the crickets. Yeah. I don't like
the sound of those crickets anymore.
Thank you.
I wish, uh...
I wish it was the sound
of something different.
Maybe, um, squawk of seagulls
or, uh, waves gently lapping on the beach.
Well, that sounds nice.
Could be real.
I'm just saying there's nothing
tying us down here anymore.
But you seem to think
our bank account is bigger than it is.
Could be.
I got a call from my buddy
in the New York days.
Montauk's looking
for a new chief of police.
Town's up and coming. It'd be 20% more.
I know that's not big enough
for a mansion or anything,
but it's... significant.
Kids would be closer.
Just a little quick trip into the city.
You and me?
We could start again.
Fresh.
Together.
Are you kidding?
We don't have to figure out
anything tonight.
We don't have to decide anything, but, um...
That's not true.
What...?
There's one thing
I would like to decide tonight.
Who's...?
At last
Joyce Byers.
My love has come along
Will you spend the rest of your life
with a tired, grumpy, stubborn old man
who loves you very much?
Yes. I will.
Oh, well, at last
The skies above are blue
My heart was wrapped up in clover
The night that I looked at you
At last
Ooh
A hushed quiet falls over the town.
Frightened villagers watch
from rooftops and alleyways, wondering,
how will this all end?
The sound of boots echo across the square
as Strahd von Zarovich strides up
to Dustin the Bard.
- Don't do this.
- The vampire lord lunges.
- No!
- Plunging its fangs into his throat.
Onlookers gasp as his body collapses.
His lute clatters across the cobblestone,
letting out a final mournful note.
Son of a bitch!
A lone hero remains, Will the Wise,
Barovia's last and only hope.
Cast Meteor Swarm. Take out the bastard.
- I can't.
- Why not?
He's in the range
of the suppression stone. No magic.
Then just whack him with your staff.
And inflict six points of damage.
He has 30 HP left.
Okay, so now what?
- That's it.
- Nothing.
What do you mean, nothing?
- Checkmate.
- We lost.
So after all of that,
Strahd von Douchebag just wins?
- This game is bullshit!
- I agree.
Stupid, goddamn waste of time!
Strahd takes great pleasure in your anger.
Time to join your friends, sorcerer.
Just get it over with and roll.
I don't wanna hear his shit anymore.
All right.
The mage. From the Abbey of St. Markovia.
She said we can summon her.
When at our lowest depth.
The incantation to summon her.
What's the incantation?
- What is the incantation?
- Will! Will!
"Oh, mage! Arise and end our fall
from darkened paths and secrets deep."
"Come forth and help your promise keep."
Nothing happens.
- Come on, man.
- Why?
Then why do we even have the incantation?
- What?
- Wait.
Wait, wait.
A purple light begins to shine
through the mist.
Growing brighter and brighter.
It's a portal.
And out of this portal steps...
the Mage of St. Markovia!
The mage holds out her hands, and shoom,
a beam of powerful light shoots forward.
Strahd lets out a piercing...
...as his body shrivels, burns,
and turns to ash.
Bada-boom!
How do you like that?
Whoo!
The misty gloom that shrouds the village
of Barovia evaporates,
and you are met
with cheers from the townsfolk.
In honor of your courage and bravery,
they give you medals,
and you are all awarded
1,000 pieces of gold each.
Flush with wealth and honor,
you live out the rest of your lives
in comfort and in happiness.
Aaaaah!
The end.
- Great campaign.
- Good campaign, buddy.
Great campaign.
Wait, wait, wait. Hold on. That's it?
Comfort and happiness?
Could you be more trite?
I thought you were some kind
of master storyteller or something.
Oh.
Well, it is true,
the comfort and happiness part.
But happiness can be found in many places.
The knight and the zoomer,
they retire from battle,
and they settle down in a small village.
With each passing day,
their love grows stronger.
The bard,
craving knowledge,
makes his way
to the Mage's Guild of Enclave,
where he spends his days
in their vast library.
- Though deeply devoted to his studies...
- Hey, buddy.
...he still makes time
for the occasional adventure.
As for Will the Wise,
he travels far and long
to the bustling city of Vallaki.
It's overwhelming at first.
So very different
from the village where he spent his youth.
But it isn't long
before he finds his place there.
Hey!
And with that, deep happiness
and acceptance.
And the storyteller? What about him?
The storyteller keeps telling stories,
stories inspired by his friends.
One day, he hopes
their tales of grand adventure
will spread far and wide across the land
so all can know of their great bravery.
But there is a story
that he can never tell.
The story of the mage.
Or at least not the real story.
The real story?
When she cast Sunbeam.
Get off me!
Goodbye, Mike.
She expended the last of her energy,
and she vanished.
El!
But has anyone asked themselves
how she cast that spell?
The suppression stone.
She couldn't have used her magic.
In the excitement, no one even noticed.
But you see, the mage is very clever.
A cleverness only matched by her sister,
who, upon hearing the pleads
of the paladin,
had a change of heart.
Don't cry, Jane.
My story...
was always going to end here.
But yours doesn't have to.
Together, the sisters devised a plan,
a plan to protect the mage
from the Order of the Black Hand,
who remained hell-bent
on stealing her powers.
So in order to trick them,
she had to make everyone,
including her friends,
believe that she was dead.
And so the sister cast a spell
from far away.
Safe from the power
of the suppression stone.
El! Do you see El?
A spell of invisibility.
Once the mage escaped,
the sister cast one final spell.
The mage you saw die was not real.
She was an illusion.
Where did she go?
No one knows.
No one will ever know.
But I'd... I'd like to imagine that she's
in a beautiful land, somewhere far away.
She finds a small town to call home.
Safe from the danger of the Black Hand.
And it is here,
at last,
that she finds peace.
That she finally finds happiness.
And this is just a theory, right?
How do we know it's true?
We don't.
Not for sure.
But I choose to believe that it is.
I believe.
Guys! What's going on?
The lasagna's getting cold!
Yeah, we... we just finished.
We'll be right up.
- Holly, how do we play this game?
- Jesus, watch out!
Jeez yourself!
You said you'd be done an hour ago!
Look, it's our own little castle.
I'll look in the manual
for like a starter campaign in here.
Why do you get to be Dungeon Master?
Because this was my idea,
and this is my house!
You told me
this was not going to be nerdy!
- This is super nerdy!
- Put him down!
- Did you just fart?
- No.
Something smells. I'm gonna puke.
It's just old pizza.
Old pizza doesn't smell like crusty ass!
Blame it on the girls.
Excuse me, girls don't fart.
If they do, it smells like roses.
Listen to Holly!
- You get these back when you focus!
- I can't see!
Okay! You can be a halfling! A halfling!
You want me to walk around like this
and fall over?
No, you're sitting down and focusing!
Give me my glasses back!
I
I wish you could swim
Like the dolphins
Like dolphins can swim
Though nothing
Nothing will keep us together
We can beat them forever and ever
Oh, we can be heroes
Just for one day
I
I will be king
And you
You will be queen
Though nothing
Will drive them away
We can be heroes
Just for one day
We can be us
I
- I can remember
- I remember
Standing
- By the wall
And the guns
- Shot above our heads
- Over our heads
And we kissed
- As though nothing could fall
- Nothing could fall
And the shame
Was on the other side
Oh, we can beat them
Forever and ever
Then we can be heroes
Just for one day
We can be heroes